# DANA MCKEE



dana.m.mckee@gmail.com



604.671.4896



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/dana-m-mckee



https://github.com/danammckee/Projects

# SKILLS

#### **Software**

- Adobe Illustrator 2020
- AutoCAD Map 3D 2020 10.6.0
- Avenza MAPublisher
- ESRI Suite: AGOL, Enterprise,
- ArcGIS Pro 2.7.1, Desktop 10.7.1, ArcGIS Developers, ArcGIS Survey 123
- FME Desktop 2020 1.2.1
- Google Maps: API, Cloud Platform
- Mapbox
- Microsoft: Access, SQL Server, Office 365
- Oracle Spatial 12c
- PCI Geomatica
- PostgresSQL 13.2
- Seequent Leapfrog Geo
- Visual Studio Code

#### Languages

- Arcade
- CSS
- HTML
- JavaScript
- Python
- SQL

#### Other

- **AWS**
- **Database Management**
- Github
- **REST API**
- Web Design
- **Event Planning**
- **Public Speaking**
- Workshop Development

 $oldsymbol{\mathsf{G}}$  IS Applications Specialist graduate with a passion for telling stories enhanced by my technical expertise and skillset. Along with my background in Geology, Education, Performing Arts, and Event Planning, I have developed a keen sense of how all the small details work together to build the big picture.

## EDUCATION

## **Graduate Certificate GIS Applications Specialist**

Sir Sandford Fleming College, 2020-2021

#### **B.Sc. Environmental Geoscience**

Simon Fraser University, 2013-2016

# PROJECTS AND EXAMPLE WORK

To view projects and example work please visit: https://danammckee.github.io/Projects/index.html

# RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

## **GIS Applications Developer**

### The Liberty Project | Lindsay, Ontario | February 2021 - Present

- Managed the development of an event platform as a website for the client's fundraising event that allowed public donations, event registration and public engagement.
- Collaborated in a team to develop a custom interactive scollytelling web map using Mapbox and JavaScript for the client's website that follows the route while engaging and informing the audience about the nonprofit.
- Oversaw the development of a custom Access database management system and VBA based ETL process to maintain the client's donor and registrant information.
- https://www.the-libertyproject.org/ride-4-freedom (Live June 30th)

# National Operations Manager | Social Media Manager | BC Volunteer

#### Canadian Improv Games | Canada | August 2009 - Present

- Worked remotely for national charity and supported a distributed team locally and nationally to effectively organize and execute live events, develop and present training workshops, recruit new teams, and oversee the national volunteer bodies.
- Acted as Media Liaison with CBC to help produce and organize the production, filming, and screening of the documentary, The 2019 Canadian Improv Games with Andrew Phung.
- Produces yearly improv programming including workshops, live shows, and acts in number of roles such as show host, planner, social media coordinator, and workshop developer.

# DANA MCKEE



dana.m.mckee@gmail.com



604.671.4896



https://www.linkedin.com/in/dana-m-mckee



https://github.com/danammckee/Projects

#### CERTIFICATES

#### **Cartography MOOC**

ESRI, 2021

## **Creating Optimized Routes Using ArcGIS Pro**

ESRI, 2021

## Introduction to ArcGIS for Server **REST API**

ESRI, 2021

## **Performing Spatial Interpolation Using ArcGIS**

ESRI, 2021

# **Preparing for Network Analysis**

ESRI, 2021

#### **Leapfrog Works Fundamentals**

Seequent, 2018

## **Certified Master Tutor**

College Reading & Learning Association, 2016

#### JI Live Leadership &

#### **Communication Certificate**

Justice Institute of British Columbia, 2016

## AWARDS

# The Association of Ontario Land **Surveyors Education Foundation GIS Award**

Exemplified leadership in project management, 2021

# **Geologist | Community Volunteer**

#### SGDS Hive Geological Consulting & Below BC | Vancouver, BC | April 2017 - July 2019

- Worked in the office and field to record, interpret, analyze, and generate technical reports on the geological deposition in various locations in Canada.
- Collaborated with numerous companies to develop long-term plans on creating sustainable practices within the resource mining industry.
- Developed and presented educational programming for all ages at public events such as the Vancouver Gem and Mineral Show, Richmond BC Library, EGBC Day, Vancouver Round Up, Britannia Mine, Resources for Future Generations, and Geoscience BC.

## **Program Planner**

#### Justice Institute of British Columbia | Vancouver, BC | September 2016 - May 2018

- Accurately identified educational program requirements, scheduled courses and instructors, and worked to optimize system processes to promote student success.
- Managed the Centre's marketing activities and promotional tactics including production of the Centre's Yearly Viewbook in collaboration with the Communications & Marketing department.
- Organized and facilitated leadership workshops and engagement activities for the school staff as a member of the JIBC Live Committee.

## **Learning Centre Services Coordinator | Tutor**

#### Douglas College | New Westminster, BC | September 2012 - January 2017

- Coordinated daily operation and marketing initiatives of the Learning Centre including payroll and budgeting, scheduling, and oversaw the peer tutors.
- Developed and delivered engaging individual and group learning sessions for over 600 students a semester, in-person and online, for university students, tailored to individual needs in science and mathematics.
- Member of the Student Leadership Programs Committee where various departments identified gaps and developed programs to provide training skills for student leaders on campus.

## **Gym Lead Director | Marketing Director**

## Coquitlam Dodgeball League | Coquitlam, BC | August 2008 - April 2019

- Coordinated and supervised the Gym Lead volunteers, organized the weekly schedule, and acted as a mediator to guide and support teams and players.
- Developed multiple onboarding processes including those for new volunteers into the executive volunteer body, new teams and players into the league, and how to become a league referee.